(Howard:)I think it's weird.
(Bernadette:)Howie?
(Howard:)It is. He's a grown man.
(Howard:)He's just gonna
live there rent-free?
(Howard:)How is that gonna motivate him
(Howard:)to get off his butt
and get a job?
(Howard:)I mean, do you even have a plan?
(Stuart:)Hey, you're not my father, okay?
(Stuart:)And besides, your mother
and I were talking...
"Your mother and I"?
You're not my father!
I didn't say I was your father!
(Howard:)Well, I didn't say
I was your father!
Okay, calm down.
(Bernadette:)You're not his father,
he's not your father!
(Bernadette:)Nobody's anybody's father.
I-I'm sorry
you don't like my life choices,
but it's my life!
(Howard:)Well, it's my house,
it's my rules!
Oh-oh! Okay, Dad!
(Stuart:)If I mow the lawn,
can I have my allowance?
(Bernadette:)Hey, don't you take that
sarcastic tone with him!
(Sheldon:)I don't have
to listen to you!
Don't talk to her like that!
That is my mother... Wife!
My wife! I said my wife!
(Raj:)You know what?
(Stuart:)This isn't getting us anywhere.
(Stuart:)When you're ready to apologize,
you know where to find me.
Well, yeah, in my house!
That's right, sucka!
(Sheldon:)I wish I'd never
gone on that trip.